### Contact

labryson32@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/lacheriavanburen-417775125 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Nursing Healthcare Management Hospitals

### Certifications

Basic Life Support for Healthcare Providers (BLS)

Advanced Registered Nurse Practitioner

# LaCheria VanBuren

Clinic Manager Rediclinic- Family Nurse Practitioner Pearland

## Summary

Advanced Nursing has given me the professional scope to diagnose, prescribe, and manage the overall care of a patient. I believe in promoting health, and disease prevention, in addition to helping during periods of acute illness. My commitment is to caring for patients and the ability to provide high quality patient care to make a valuable contribution to the tradition of excellence. I have two years experience as an Clinic Manager, four years experience as an Family Nurse Practitioner, and five years experience as an Registered Nurse.

## Experience

RediClinic Clinical Manager October 2017 - Present (2 years 11 months) Houston, Texas Area

Shadow Creek Medical Clinic Nurse Practitoner September 2016 - October 2017 (1 year 2 months) Pearland, Texas

Harris Health System
Registered Nurse
May 2013 - September 2016 (3 years 5 months)

## Education

Prairie View A&M University

Master's Degree in Science, Family Practice Nurse/Nursing · (2014 - 2016)